Guide to the Elmer J. Holland Papers, 1937-1968 AIS.1968.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Special Files, IV.
  - Elections, 1.
    - List of elected officials in 30th Congressional District, October 21,1964 (Box 205, Folder 7)
    - Campaign material (Box 206, Folder 1-3)
    - Congratulations (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - Holland for Congress, 1965 (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - Voters Registration Statistics, 1965 (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Primary Correspondence, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Nominating petitions, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Campaign contributions, 1966 (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Campaign material, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Election Statistics, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Voters registration, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Holland for Congress Committee, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Endorsements, 1966 (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - General, Street list of electors, 1966 (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh -15th Ward -Districts 1 20 (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh 16th Ward Districts 1-15 (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh 17th Ward Districts 1-10 (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh - 18th Ward (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Pittsburgh 29th Ward (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh 30th Ward (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Pittsburgh 31st Ward (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Braddock Borough Wards 1-4 (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Braddock Hills, Boro Wards 1 and 2 (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Chalfant Borough (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Clairton 1st Ward, Districts 1-3 and 2nd Ward, Districts 1-10 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Dravosburg Borough, Districts 1-4 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Duquesne 1st Ward, Districts 1-5, 2nd and 3rd Wards, Districts 1-4 (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - Glassport Borough (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - East McKeesport Borough (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - East Pittsburgh Borough (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Elizabeth Borough (Box 209, Folder 18)
    - Homestead Borough 3rd Ward, Districts 1-4, 4th Ward, Districts 1-3, and 5th Ward, Districts 1-3 (Box 209, Folder 19)
    - Lincoln Borough (Box 209, Folder 20)
    - McKeesport City (Box 209, Folder 21)
    - Mt. Oliver Borough Districts 1-6 (Box 209, Folder 22)
    - Munhall Borough, Districts 1-12 (Box 209, Folder 23)
    - North Braddock Borough 1st Ward, Districts 1-5, 2nd Ward, Districts 1-2, and 3rd Ward, Districts 1-3 (Box 209, Folder 24)
    - Port Vue Borough, Districts 1-6 (Box 209, Folder 25)
    - Rankin Borough Districts 1-6 (Box 209, Folder 26)
    - Swissvale Borough Districts 1-15 (Box 209, Folder 27)
    - Trafford Borough (First Election District) (Box 209, Folder 28)
    - Turtle Creek Borough 1st Ward, Districts 1-3, 2nd Ward, Districts 1-3, and 3rd Ward, Districts 1-3 (Box 209, Folder 29)
    - Versailles Borough, Districts 1-2 (Box 209, Folder 30)
    - Wall Borough (Box 209, Folder 31)
    - West Homestead Borough, Districts 1-4 (Box 209, Folder 32)
    - West Mifflin Borough, Districts 1-19 (Box 209, Folder 33)
    - Whitaker Borough, Districts 1-3 (Box 209, Folder 34)
    - White Oak Borough, Districts 1-7 (Box 209, Folder 35)
    - Wilmerding Borough, Wards 1-4 (Box 209, Folder 36)
    - Elizabeth Township, Wards 1-9 (Box 209, Folder 37)
    - Forward Township, Districts 1-3 (Box 209, Folder 38)
    - North Versailles Township, Wards 1-7 (Box 209, Folder 39)
    - South Versailles Township (Box 209, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, election returns, newspaper clippings, 1967 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 2-4)
    - General Campaign material, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Voter registration statistics, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - List of elected officials, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Primary Petitions, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1968 (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - Lists of elected officials 30th Congressional, 1960 (Box 210, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 210, Folder 11)
  - Local Community. Records., 2.
    The Local Community Records Subseries contains local community records by location including the correspondence, reports, and research data on those communities.
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Appalachia Grants and Loans under education acts (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Federal Funds 20th Congressional District (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Job Opportunities Contracts Department of Labor (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Poverty Allegheny County (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Poverty Pennsylvania State Grants, etc. (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Poverty Program Information for Congressman Holland. 20th Congressional District (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: OEO Program Information (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Office of Economic Opportunity. Poverty. (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Public Works Allegheny County. (APW) (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Urban Renewal (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Urban Renewal. Allegheny County, 1967 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - ALLEGHENY COUNTY: Urban Renewal. Allegheny County Port Authority (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Braddock. Education ESEA Schools (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Braddock General Hospital (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Braddock Poverty (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Braddock Sewage Disposal (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Braddock Urban Renewal. Automated Storage (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Braddock Hills (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Braddock Hills. Public Works. Sewage Disposal. (APW). (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - CHARDIN CENTRE. Poverty. (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - CHALFONT BOROUGH. Public Works. (APW). (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Clairton General (Box 212, Folder 10-11)
    - Clairton Appalachia (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Clairton Housing (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Clairton Poverty (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Clairton Public Library (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Clairton Public Works (APW) CFA (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Clairton Sewage Disposal (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Dravosburg (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Dravosburg. Public Works (APW) (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Dravosburg. Sewage Disposal (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Dravosburg Dwellings. Public Housing. (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Duquesne (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - Appalachia (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - Duquesne Highway (Box 212, Folder 24)
    - Duquesne Housing (Box 212, Folder 25)
    - Duquesne Poverty (Box 212, Folder 26)
    - Duquesne Public Works (APW) (Box 212, Folder 27)
    - Duquesne Schools (Box 212, Folder 28)
    - Duquesne Sewage Disposal (Box 212, Folder 29)
    - Duquesne Urban Renewal (Box 212, Folder 30-31)
    - Elizabeth Borough. Dept. of Interior. Bureau of Recreation (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Elizabeth Borough. (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Elizabeth Borough and Elizabeth Township. Sewage Disposal. (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Elizabeth Township (Box 213, Folder 4-5)
    - Elizabeth Dam (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth Township. Public Works. (APW) (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth Forward Schools (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Forward Township. Public Works. (APW) Sewage (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Public Works. Re: Sealed Mines Affecting Well Water (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Sewage Disposal (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - GLEN HAZEL HEIGHTS Public Housing (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Glassport Public Works (APW) (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - GLASSPORT Senior Citizen Housing (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - GLASSPORT Sewage Disposal (Box 213, Folder 15-16)
    - HOMESTEAD General (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Homestead Hospital (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - Homestead Housing (Box 213, Folder 19-20)
    - Homestead Poverty (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - Homestead Schools (Box 213, Folder 22)
    - Homestead Urban Redevelopment (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - Liberty Boro (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Appalachia (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Liberto Boro Public Works (APW) (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Liberty Boro Sewage Disposal (Box 213, Folder 27)
    - Lincoln Borough (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Appalachia (Box 213, Folder 29)
    - Lincoln Borough Public Works (APW) Sewage (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - McKeesport (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Articles on City of McKeesport (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - McKeesport Chamber of Commerce (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - McKeesport Naval Reserve Center (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - McKeesport Office Lease, equipment, supplies (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - McKeesport Postmaster. Re: Appt. of Frank A. Todd (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - McKeesport Post Office. (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Poverty McKeesport. "Mon Yough Committee for the War Against Poverty." (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Neighborhood Centers Proposal. Mon Yough Community Action Committee, Inc. (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Pre Vocational Opportunity Center for the Handicapped. Mon Yough Community Action Committee, Inc. (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Public Works. McKeesport (APW) (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - McKeesport Redevelopment (Box 215, Folder 5-7)
    - Sewage Disposal McKeesport (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Urban Renewal McKeesport (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - MCKEES ROCKS Urban Renewal (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Monroeville Mine Fire and Sewage (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Monroeville Public Works (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Monroeville Sewage Disposal (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - MOUNT OLIVER BOROUGH (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Munhall (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Appalachia (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Munhall Interior Dept. Outdoor Recreation Project. (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Munhall Public Works (APW) (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - North Braddock Borough (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - North Braddock Public Works (APW) (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - North Braddock Urban Renewal (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - North Versailles (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - North Versailles Post Office (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - North Versailles. Rent Supplement (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - North Versailles Public Works. (APW) Sewage Disposal (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - North Versailles Public Works (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - PITCAIRN Public Works. Open Space (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Pittsburgh APW EDA (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Department of Justice. Law Enforcement Grant Pittsburgh. (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - Poverty Program Pittsburgh (Mayor's Committee on Human Resources). (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - SOUTH SIDE Pittsburgh Urban Renewal (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - PORT VUE BOROUGH: Appalachia (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - PORT VUE BOROUGH: Public Works (APW) (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - PORT VUE BOROUGH: Port Vue Liberty Joint School District. Ship's Bells for Church. (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - PORT VUE BOROUGH: Sewage Disposal (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - RANKIN: Demonstration Cities (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - RANKIN: Educational Grant (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - RANKIN: Poverty (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - RANKIN: Public Works (APW) (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - RANKIN: Urban Renewal (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - SWISSVALE: Appalachia (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - SWISSVALE: Public Works (APW) (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - SWISSVALE: Urban Renewal (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Snowden Sewage Disposal (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - Turtle Creek (Box 217, Folder 15-16)
    - Turtle Creek: Appalachia (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - Turtle Creek: Appropriations, correspondence, etc. Flood Control, 1960. (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - Turtle Creek: Public Housing (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - Turtle Creek Valley. Model Cities. "Model Cities Plan for Turtle Creek Valley." (Box 217, Folder 20)
    - Public Works Turtle Creek and Thompson Run Sewer Project Joint. Wilkins and Churchill (Box 217, Folder 21)
    - Turtle Creek School Board (Box 217, Folder 22)
    - Turtle Creek Urban Renewal (Box 217, Folder 23)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - The Case for the Conemaugh Dam. Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control, 1956-1959 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Flood Control, February 1956 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. BIDS (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. Borough Resolutions. (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Turtle Creek. Flood Control Chartiers Creek (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Flood Control. Corps of Engineers, news releases, misc. (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control Form Letters. (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Turtle Creek Flood Control. Files of Congressman Frank Buchanan and Congresswoman Vera Buchanan. (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - VERSAILLES BOROUGH. Public Works (APW) (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - WALL BOROUGH (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - West Mifflin Borough (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Appalachia (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - West Mifflin BORO House Senate Bills re Payment in Lieu of Tax Committee Reports (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - West Mifflin Mine Subsidence, July 15, 1968 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - West Mifflin. Open Space. (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - West Mifflin. Payment in lieu of Taxes (Westinghouse Bettis Plant), 1957 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - West Mifflin Post Office, 1949-1955 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - WEST MIFFLIN Poverty. (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - WEST MIFFLIN Public Housing (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - WEST MIFFLIN Public Works (APW) (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - West Mifflin BORO Schools (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - West Mifflin Boro Schools, Prior to 1956. (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - West Mifflin Sewage Disposal (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - WHITAKER BORO. Public Works. (APW) (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - White Oak Borough (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - White Oak Borough Public Works (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - White Oak Borough Urban Renewal (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - WILKINSBURG PENN. Public Works. Joint Water Authority. (Box 220, Folder 20)
    - Wilmerding (Box 220, Folder 21)
    - Wilmerding Urban Renewal (Box 220, Folder 22)
  - Subject File, 3.
    The Subject File Subseries is a subject file of people, places, and organizations and reference material used in researching background information.
    - A-General (Box 221, File-cabinet 1-2)
    - Accelerated Public Works (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - ALLEGHENY County (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - Chalfont (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - Clairton (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - Dravosburg (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - Duquesne (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - East Pittsburgh (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - East McKeesport (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - Elizabeth (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - Forward (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - Glassport (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - Homestead (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - Lincoln (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - Munhall (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - North Braddock (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - North Versailles (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - Port Vue (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - Rankin (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - Swissvale (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - Turtle Creek (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - Versailles (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - West Mifflin (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - White Oak (Box 221, Folder 24)
    - Wilmerding (Box 221, Folder 25)
    - Agency of International Development (A.I.D.) (Box 221, Folder 26)
    - A.I.D. and Department of State (Box 221, Folder 27)
    - Action Housing, Pittsburgh, Pa. (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture, Department (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture. Pictures and Biographies (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture Yearbook Requests, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - AIR Control. Pittsburgh Airport. (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Airport Pittsburgh Airport (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Air Pollution (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Allegheny County (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - Allegheny County Airport (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - Allegheny County Schools. Dr. Beattie. (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - Allegheny County Unemployed on Relief, 1962 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - Allegheny County. Community Action Program Conference, September 30, 1968 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - Allegheny County. Labor Council. (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - Allegheny Redevelopment Authority (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - Americans for Democratic Action (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - A.F. of L. and C.I.O. (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - AFL Building and Construction Trades Department. (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - American Policy (Box 223, Folder 17)
    - Appalachia (Box 224, Folder 1-2)
    - Appalachia Information (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Appalachia, 1965 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Appalachian Act Amendment, 1967 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Archives (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Area Redevelopment Act (Box 224, Folder 7)
    - Area Redevelopment Agency. Correspondence. (Box 224, Folder 8)
    - A.R.A., 1962 (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - A.R.A., 1962-1963 (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - A.R.A., 1963 (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - A.R.A. Braddock (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - A.R.A. Schnabel Company (Box 225, Folder 5)
    - Army Fact Sheets on Military Policies (Box 225, Folder 6)
    - Army Engineers. Re: Water Supply Northeastern United States, Water Supply Study. (Box 225, Folder 7)
    - Army Navy Game, 1960. (Box 225, Folder 8)
    - Army Navy Game, November 27, 1966 (Box 225, Folder 9)
    - Army Navy Ticket Requests, 1955-1958 (Box 225, Folder 10)
    - Army Navy Tickets, 1963 (Box 225, Folder 11)
    - Atomic Energy Commission. (Box 225, Folder 12)
    - Automation (Box 225, Folder 13)
    - B General (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Banking (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Barber License in Pennsylvania (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Bethel Park Convalescent Home (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Birch Society, 1962 (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Birchers and such (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Birth Control (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Blind Seeing Eye Dog Information (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Boy Scouts (Box 226, Folder 9)
    - Boy and Girl Scouts, 1966 (Box 226, Folder 10)
    - Braddock (Box 226, Folder 11)
    - Broadcasting (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Bruceton, Blast Furnace. Closing, 1966 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 1962 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 1963 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1968 (Box 227, Folder 5)
    - Builders (Box 227, Folder 6)
    - Bureau of Employment Security (Box 227, Folder 7)
    - Business (Box 227, Folder 8)
    - Business, 1962-1963 (Box 227, Folder 9)
    - Business Subsidy (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Business Views (Box 227, Folder 11)
    - C-General (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
    - Cabinet Members (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Captive Nations (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Carnegie College. General, 1965-1966 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Castro, Fidel of Cuba (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Census (correspondence) (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Census (Printed material) (Box 228, Folder 8-9)
    - Census Population, 1950 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - Census Positions Information, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Census Results, 1960 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - CIA (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - Chamber of Commerce (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Chamber of Commerce Meeting, January 23, 1962 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1963 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Chamber of Commerce Views (Box 229, Folder 4)
    - Chamber of Commerce Pittsburgh Officials (Box 229, Folder 5)
    - Cherry Blossom Festival (Box 229, Folder 6)
    - Churches 30th District (Box 229, Folder 7)
    - Citation Certification. Bills Lobby Committee (Box 229, Folder 8)
    - Citizens Against Communism (Box 229, Folder 9)
    - Citizenship Clearing House of Western Pennsylvania (Box 229, Folder 10)
    - City Tax (Box 229, Folder 11)
    - Civil Defense (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Civil Defense (Defense Mobilization) (Box 230, Folder 2-3)
    - Civil Rights (Box 230, Folder 4-5)
    - Civil Rights Report (100 years), 1963 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - Civil Service Commission (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Civil War Centennial Material, 1961-1965 (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Closed Court Cases (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Coal (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Commendation, Letter of/to various individuals (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Commerce, Department of (Box 231, Folder 1-4)
    - Commerce, Pictures and Biographies (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - COPE Committee for National Trade Policy (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - COPE, Committee on Political Education, 1962 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Communism (Box 231, Folder 8-9)
    - Department of Community Affairs, Urban Renewal, Urban Planning, Research (Box 231, Folder 10)
    - Programs, Housing, Project 70, Mass Transit, Appalachia (Box 231, Folder 11)
    - Community College, Allegheny County (Box 231, Folder 12)
    - Congratulations sent out. (Box 231, Folder 13)
    - Congressional Voting, 1947-1956 (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Voting Record through the 84th Congress (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Congressional Voting Record. 88th Congress, 1st Session (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Congress. First Session. 87th Congress (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - 87th Congress CIO Organization Plan, 1953 (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - CIO Ruether Report, 1955 (Box 231, Folder 7)
    - Congressional Directory (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Interns (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Record. 90th Congress. Mailing List. (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Congressmen Pennsylvania. Alphabetical List. (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Contracts Copperweld (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Contracts Correspondence (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Congressional Reorganization (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Contracts U.S. Steel (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Contracts Westinghouse (Box 232, Folder 8-9)
    - Copyright Information (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Corregidor Bataan Memorial (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - "Crank" material (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - Credit (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - Crime Juvenile Delinquency, etc. (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - Croations (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - Cuba (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Customs, Bureau (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - D General (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Defense (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Defense Contracts Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Defense Department (Box 234, Folder 4-5)
    - Defense. Pictures and Biography (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Demonstration Cities (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Denny, Harmar J. (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Disaster Loans (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Draft (Box 234, Folder 10-11)
    - Driver's License, 1963 (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - Drug Legislation, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - Democratic Party (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Democratic Party (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - E General (Box 238, Folder 1-2)
    - Economic Development Act. (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Economic Needs, 1963 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Economic Outlook (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Economic Status, 1962 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Reports economics (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Economy (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Economy, Planned, 1962 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Economy, 1962-1963 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - National Economy Picture (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Education (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Education- Pennsylvania (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Education- Pittsburgh (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1961 (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Higher Education hearings (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Education, 1968 (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Education Adult (Box 241, Folder 4-5)
    - Clippings Educational Information (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Education clippings (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Education Federal Aid, 1963 (Box 241, Folder 8)
    - Educational Inquiries material (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Education, Jr. College and Technical Education, 1963 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Education material Pennsylvania Higher Education Assistance Agency (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Medical Education Pennsylvania, 1963 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Education National Vocational Student Loan Insurance Act of 1965 (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Educational T.V. (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Educational T.V. in Pennsylvania (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Education Youth Opportunity Unemployed Adult, 1963 (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Eisenhower Releases on Middle East State of the Union (Box 242, Folder 9)